Did you see it? I think I got it,
看到了吗? 我想我射到它了
That little piggy was fast,
那只小猪跑得真快
Hey, everybody, this is all of our kill, We all take credit,
各位 这是大家一起杀的 我们一起分享荣光
-I got a side ache, -You hit Enmebaragesi,
-我跑得肚子好痛 -你射到恩米巴拉格西了
I'm pretty sure he had that when he left the village,
我确定他从村庄出来时 背上就有了
That's not my spear,
那不是我的矛
What're you talking about,my spear has feathers...,Okay, that one's got a feather,
吕 好 那支也有玖毛
Okay, that is my spear, I'm sorry, man,
好 那是我的矛 老兄 对不起
Great, Two spears, Twice the killing power,
太好了 两支矛 杀伤力两倍
Thanks a lot, Next time don't block my shot,
多谢了 下次别挡我射猪
What? I didn't say-- Come on, not my fault,
怎么?我没说… 拜托 这不是我的错
Who stands in front of a boar ona hunt?
谁打猫时会站在野猪前面?
Hey, there you are,
你在这里
I don't think you wanna be gathered, You wanna be eaten,
我认为你不想被采集 你想被吃掉
Well, there won't be any berries in the fruit salad now, so we all lose,
水果色拉没莓子可加了 这是我们的损失
Hey, Oh, How's it going?
你好吗?
Hunters think they're so cool, You know, they--
猎人们自以为很栈 你知道的 他们…
..and put it in the basket,
把它放在篮子里
What's it,they're picking on you?
他们在找你的砖吗?
If they're picking on you, I will straighten them out,
要是他们找你的夸 我就去和他们算账
-All right, Yeah, would you? -You're right,
-好 有 你会去吗? -你说的对
Let it slide this time,
这次就放过他们
Next time, though, they will feel the tip of my short spear,
不过下次 我就让他们溉尝短矛的滋味
-What happened to your spear? -l modified it, Made it a snub nose,
-你的矛怎么了? -我改造了 让它短一点
It's lighter, It's a better killing tool, Anyway...,
这样比较轻 比较好用 反正…
Oh, there's Maya, I'm gonna go talk to her,
玛雅在那里 我要去和她说话
I'll be right back, Unless something goes horribly right,
我马上回来 除非出了什么事
-Hello, Maya, -Hey, Zed,
-你好 玛雅 -你好 柴德
What do I gotta do to make you my woman?
我要怎么做 才能让你成为我的女人?
Look, you're a special guy, You've got a lot of personality,
听着 你很特别 你的个性很不同
When my parents were killed by that pack of wild dogs...
我爸妈被一群野狗杀死时
..you really helped me see the funny side,
你真的让我看到了有趣的那一面
"No, no! He's got my ankle!"
不 他咬到我的脚踩了
"Get off," That's your mom,
走开 那是你妈
So, yeah, you make me laugh, but that's not enough,
对 你乏我开心 但那还不够
I'm an old-fashioned kind of girl,
我是很老派的女生
I need a man who can protect me and take care of me,
我要有男人能保护我、照顾我
What do you mean? Like Marlak?
什么意思? 像是马拉? 我是说 他是村里最好的猎人
-Debatable, -People voted,
-还有争议吧 -是大家投票的
Ok,maybe I'm not the greatest hunter,
或许我不是最好的猎人
-Or gatherer, -Yes, Or gatherer,
-也不是采集者 -对 采集者也不是
Zed, those are the only two jobs that we have here,
柴德 我们只有这两种工作
I can take care of you, Does it look like I'm starving?
描可以照顾你 我看起来像握俄的样子吗?
Come on, Tell me you can say no to this,
拜托 你一定无法拒绝这个
Give it a second, Let it work on you,
再等一下 你喜欢的
Oh, yeah, Absolutely can say no to that,
没错 绝对无法拒绝这个
Maya, Can I see you later?
玛雅 我们稍后再见面?
I think I have to wash my hair,
我要去洗头
You washed your hair last year,
你去年洗过头了
Tonight, we feast,
今晚 我们举办盛宴
Maya, For you,
玛雅 给你的
Thanks, Marlak, Another severed boar's head,
马拉 谢谢 又一颗野猪头
-It's a different color, -Yeah, this one is--
-不同颜色的 -对 这一个…
-Left the tongue in, -Yeah, this is really nice, Marlak,
-还有舌头 -对 真棒 马拉
Look at Marlak flirting with Maya, He doesn't know her at all,
他完全不了解她
Head's not even the best part of the boar,
野猪最好的部分不是头
It's the back fat, stupid, Muscleheaded idiot,
是后背油 笨蛋 满身肌肉的白澳
Hi, Eema, Hi, Eema, Hi, Eema,
吵 伊玛 路 伊玛 吵 伊玛
Yeah, She doesn't even know I exist,
对 她根本不知道我存在
There's like 60 people in the village, I mean...
村子里有60个人 我是说.…
.. you have to go out of your way to not know that somebody exists,
根本没办法忽略任何人的存在
Hey, hey-- Squanto, Give me a break, would you?
史光登 饶了我好吗?
You got the whole forest,
你有整座森林可用
Why does everybody always have to take a crap right behind my hut?
为什么每个人都喜欢 在我家后面大便?
I could be wrong, I think what it is is that all the poop in the area...
我不一定是对的 但我想是因为这附近的类量…
..fertilizes the ground and it gives the leaves a softer feel for wiping,
让土壤更肥沃 也让附近叶子更柔软 擦起来更舒服
It's not that nobody respects you, I haven't heard that from everyone,
并不是大家都不尊重你 我还没听所有人这样说过
I haven't heard that,let's go
我受够了 走吧
Where are we going? We're not supposed to go this far,
我们要去哪里? 我们不该走离村庄这么远
-You know what I'm gonna do? -Change villages,
-你知道我要怎么做吗? -换个村子
No, I'm gonna change my head,
不 我要换个头
I don't think that's possible, Your head is attached to your body,
那是不可能的 你的头和在你的身体上
Not the whole head, I mean, my mind,
不是整颗头 我是说我的头脑
Mind--
头脑…
Don't tell me you're thinking about eating forbidden fruit,
别告诉我你是想吃禁果
That's exactly what I'm thinking,
我正是这么想的
Zed, that's the tree of the knowledge of good and evil,
柴德 那是善恶之树
You don't eat from that one, It's forbidden,
你不能吃它的果实 那是禁忌 大家都知道
But why is it forbidden?
为什么是禁忌?
It's not the fruit, It's about the rule, It's about doing what you're told,
不是因为水果 而是因为规短 是因为他们交待的事
We've been doing what we were told our entire lives,
我们一辈子都在做别人交待的事
-How's that worked out? - like doing what I'm told,
-对我们有什么好处? -我喜欢做被交待的事
Zed, Stop, It's just a piece of fruit,
柴德 住手 这只是水果
Eating a fruit is not gonna change your life,
吃水果也不会改变你的生命
But what if it's magic fruit?
如果这是魔果呢?
That's a pretty low bar,
标准还设得蛮低的
Then all the hunters would have to bow down to me,
那所有的猎人都要臣服于我
Maya would lay with me like that,
玛雅也会和我上床
That's what this is about? Laying with Maya?
这么做的目的是什么? 和玛雅上床?
I tell you, have a great destiny, I'm about to find out what it is,
告诉你 我有伟大的使命 我要知道是什么
Can you put the fruit down, What if somebody sees us?
把水果放下 离开这里吧 要是别人看到了呢?
They'll peel our skin off and tie us to an anthill,
他们会姬了我们的皮 把我们绑在蚁窜上
It's got sort of a knowledge-y taste,
有种知识的味道
Does it have a sort of forbidden taste? That's what it is,
有没有禁忌的味道?
-Oh, I definitely feel something, -What?
-我有感觉了 -什么感觉?
Less hungry, for one, but also more intelligenter,
比较不饿了 而且更聪明了
It's like I feel like maybe I know everything,
感觉好像我无所不知了
Ask me something, Anything, Go, Test me, Go,
问我问题 什么都好 快 考考我
All right, where does the sun go at night?
好 太阳晚上去哪里了?
Pass, Next question,
束过 下一题
-Okay, where do babies come from? -Pass, Next question,
-好 宝宝从哪里来的? -跳过 下一题
-There's a snake on my foot, -In the form of a question,
-我脚上有蛇 -我叫你问问题
There's a snake on my foot?
我脚上有蛇吗?
-Correct, -What do I do?
-没错 -我要怎么办?
I got a lot of ideas, I'm bursting with ideas on the subject,
我有很多办法 关于这问题我出现许多想法
-It's constricting me, -You could stick your finger in its hole,
-它在勒我 -你可以来陈进攻
You know what, you could eat it before it eats you, Try that,
你可以在它吃掉你前先吃了它 试试看
Eat the snake first, That's what my new brain tells me,
先把蛇吃掉 我的新头脑是这么说的
-It's preparing to eat me, -Go for the eyes,
-它快要把我吃了 -先从眼睛开始
It's big,
真大条
I'm dying a virgin,
我还是处男就要死了
Wait right here, I'm gonna go eat more fruit,
等等 我再去多吃点水果
-This was a bit of a rough day for me, -Yeah, There's gotta be more to life,
-我今天真不好过 -对 生命中还有更多挑战
This is a lot, I don't think I can handle too much more than this,
这样就够了 我想我受不了 比这更严重的事了
No way, Look at these people,
才不会 看看这些人
They're like animals, We're way too good for this,
他们就像动物 我们比这好多了
Now that I'm smarter I'm going straight to the top,
现在我变聪明了 我要登上颠峰
I'm bringing you, You're gonna be my right hand,
我会带着你 你会是我的左右手
I've seen what you do with your right hand, No,thank you
我看过你的左右手做过什么事 谢了 我不要
Don't you wonder what's on the other side of the mountains?
你没想过山的另一边是什么吗?
There's nothing on the other side of the mountains, okay?
山的另一边什么也没有 好吗?
The world ends, Everybody knows that, You'd fall right off of it,
那是世界的尽头 大家都知道的 你只会掉下去
But what if it doesn't?
如果不是这样呢?
It makes my stomach go:
这让我的心里觉得…
I've been thinking a lot ever since I ate that fruit,
我吃了水果之后就想了很多
Why is there fruit? What is fruit?
为什么有水果? 水果是什么?
It's a thing that you eat, Why do we eat?
是你吃的一种东西 我们为什么要吃?
What are we? What are we? Why do I have these?
我们是什么? 我为什么有手指?
Everything is weird,
一切都好奇怪
When you really stop and look at it, everything gets very, very strange--
等你真正停下脚步看 一切都非常非常奇怪
Why am I talking? What is this?
我为什么在说话? 这是什么?
My lips make a movement and then a sound...
我的嘴唇移动 然后就有声音
..and you know what I mean,
你知道我的意思
Blows my mind,
头快想爆了
That just sounds like crazy fruit talk, I don't wanna hear it right now,
听起来像注掉的水果语 我现在不想听了
Boy, she looks nice tonight,
老天 她今晚真美
Do it, man, Dance for her,
上吧 老兄 去为她跳舞
I don't know, They're doing the jackal dance,
我不知道 他们在跳对狼手
It's not my strongest,
这不是我的强项
What, are you kidding me? You have an amazing jackal dance,
你开玩笑吗? 你对狼三跳得最好了
Go, Jackal dance,
上 和骑狠大
Get into it,
快上
Over the head,
打头
I'm gonna go and eat, I'm gonna come back,
我要去吃东西了 我会回来的
Your father was a great hunter, But you, you're like a little girl,
你和爸是个好猎人 但你就像个小女生
Good one, Marlak,
说得好 马拉
Enmebaragesi says he saw you in the garden,
恩米巴拉格西说他看到你在花园里
Really? Well, what if I told you that Enmebaragesi was a liar?
真的? 要是我说 恩米巴拉格西在说谎呢?
I saw him eat the forbidden fruit,
我看到他吃了禁果
Oh, that,
吕 那件事
-Hey, what's going on here? -[ will kill you where you stand,
-这是怎么回事? -我要就地杀了你
Oh, a shooting star, That's the best,
有流星 真美
-You really ate the fruit? -One bite, What's the big deal?
一你真的吃了水果? -一口 有什么大不了的?
You don't eat the fruit,
你不该吃水果
It's the number one rule since the beginning of time,
自万物初始 那就是第一条守则
Since the Great Turtle climbed out of the sea with Earth on its back,
自从大海包背着地球走出海面起
I know, but I'm a little fuzzy on the exact details,
我知道那是守则 但我不是很清楚 确切的细节了
You ate-- You did the one thing you're not supposed to do, Forbidden,
你吃了 你做了一件不该做的事
But the word "forbidden" implies there's a little wiggle room,
但禁忌这个词还暗指有摇摆的空间
There's no wiggle room with forbidden, You're cursed, man,
禁忌没有摇摆的空间 你被诅咒了
If you stay here, we'll all be cursed, You have to leave,
如果你待在这里 我们都会被诅唤 你得离开
-Where am I supposed to go? -I didn't eat the fruit,
-我要去哪里? -我没吃水果
My hands are tied,
我无能为力
Do I detect a little bit of jealousy because I now have...
我怎么感觉到你有点嫉妨 因为我现在有.…
..the knowledge of good and evil and you don't?
分装善恶的知识 而你没有?
You think it's easy being the shaman of the village?
你觉得当村落里的萨满很轻松吗?
Putting a bone through my face?
用骨头穿过我的脸呢?
I know we've known each other for a long time, We throw the rock around,
我知道我们认识很久了 从小一起丢石头长大的
We have fun together, man, but I can't be...,
我们在一起很快乐 兄弟 但是我不能…
Plus, wanna know something? lam high as shit right now, dude,
另外 想知道吗? 我现在超兴奋的 老兄
I just licked like three toads,
我才刚环过三只旷肾
I've been up for like 27 suns up and suns downs,
我二十七个日出日著没睡了
-Okay, -I just wanna get a meal...
-好 -我只想吃点东西…
-... wanna take a fucking nap, This is bullshit,
-打个胰 -这是一团独
You really..., You fucked the pooch on this one,
你真的…你这次真的搞砸了
-Hard, -I say what I did...
-大大的摘砸了 -我说我做的…
-..,Was a good thing, -Oh, yeah?
-是一件好事 -是吗?
Yeah, Really, really very good thing,
对 非常非常好的事
And I should know because I have the knowledge of good and evil,
因为我有分准善恶的知识 所以我知道
.. when I know what I'm saying is what I know what I'm saying,
当我说我知道我说我知道的时候 我在说什么
-Good, -And I'm not leaving,
-很好 -还有我不要离开
You better get out of here,
你最好离开这里
Okay, but before I go, I just wanna say one thing,
好 但在我离开前 我要再说一件事
I know I'm not the greatest hunter,
我知道我不是最好的猫人
-Or gatherer, -Or gatherer, Thank you,
-也不是采集者 -也不是采集者 谢谢你们
But there's gotta be more to life than this,
不过我的生命应该会更精彩
I'm going, but because I choose to,
我要走了 但我是自愿离开的
And anyone who wants to join me is welcome,
如果有人想跟我一起走 欢迎你
I don't know where we're going, but I will lead us,
我不知道我们会去哪里 但我会带领我们
Yeah, light up the darkness,
对 照亮黑暗
So who's with me?
谁要和我一起走?
Anyone?
有人吗?
Anyone named Oh?
有叫欧仔的人吗?
Okay, Looks like I'm gonna be going it alone,
好 看来我要独自离开了
Which is fine with me,
我没问题
.. because having a partner would just probably slow me down,
因为有人作伴只会拖慢我的速度
I'm gonna start a new tribe, 10 times better,
我要开辟新的部落 比这好上十信
There's gonna be 10 times more dancing and fun,
十倍多的跳三玩乐
It's gonna be called Muscle Tribe of Danger and Excellence,
它会叫做刺激危险的肌肉部落
And you're not invited, I don't even like any of you guys, I never did,
你们都不会被邀请 我根本不喜欢你们 从来就不喜欢
Unless anyone changes their mind, Does anyone wanna come better?
除非有人政变心意 有人想来吗?
-We're good, -Fine, Good, Bye-bye,
-没有 -好 很好 再见
Don't-- Nobody panic,
别…大家别惊慌
No! That's-- That's-- Oh, it's not my house,
不 那…那不是我家
I see you,
我看到你了
Go away, Marlak,
马拉 走开
-Really, animal noises? -Badger,
-真的? 是动物在叫吗? -是获
This is just insulting, It's time I killed you,
真是侮恨人 是该杀了你的时候了
Fine, But then, tell me this: Who's that behind you?
好 但先告诉我 谁在你背后?
You think I'm gonna turn around? I'm gonna gut you like a pig,
你以为我会转身吗? 我要把你当猪一样控出内及
Nice whack on the head, You should try hitting Eema that hard,
这一棒打得好 打伊玛也该打那么大力才对
We can discuss that later, We should run away,
这晚点再讨论 我们该逃跑了
Yes, yes, of course,
对 对 没错
So you decided to come after all, Was it the speech?
你还是决定要跟来了 是因为我讲的话吗?
I wish we didn't have to leave,
但愿我们不需要离开
That's not true, We'll go back,
才不是真的 我们会回去的
Those hunters are idiots,
那些猎人是白阁
They're gonna forget the whole thing in an hour,
他们一小时后就什么都忘了
Will you get real, man? There's no going back, okay?
你能面对现实吗? 我们回不去了 好吗?
There's nothing to go back to, It's just ashes,
回去也没什么了 只剩灰
Like it's hard to build one of those huts,
说得好像那些屋子很难搭一样
It's just a pile of sticks and dung,
那只是一堆树枝和大便
Well, you're a pile of sticks and dung,
你才是一堆树枝和大便
-I'm sorry, I-- -It's okay,
-对不起 我… -没关系
-I don't mean that, obviously, -l know you're mad...
-我不是有意的 -我知道你很生气
...but this is a great opportunity for us,
但这对我们来说是大好的机会
They didn't appreciate you back there,
他们也不了解你的好
You're the genius who thought up drinking water from a gourd,
你是个天才 想到拿戎芦喝水
They were all drinking from their hands,
他们都是用手喝水的
We have an incredible destiny,
我们的命运很神奇
You don't even know where we are, We're lost,
你根本不知道我们在哪里 我们迷路了
Of course I know where we are,
我当然知道我们在哪里
It's a cougar, Don't move a muscle,
是美洲狮 千万不要动
-What do we do? -Don't move your lips,
-我们要怎么办? -连嘴唇也别动
Rule number one: Show no fear,
守则一 别表现出丽惧
You're showing fear,
你表现出恶惧了
Much better, Very good,
好多了 非常好
-Now what? -There's two opinions on this one,
-现在怎么办? -现在有两种选择
Some say run, others say stay perfectly still,
有些人说要跑 其他人说最好保持不动
-Which one are you gonna do? -I'm going to run!
-你要选哪一个? -我选跑
You should put some maggots on those scratches,
你应该在那些抓伤上放点蛆
They look pretty deep,
看起来很深
They are very deep, That's why they appear that way,
是很深 所以才长这样
-You're still mad at me, aren't you? -l wish hadn't come,
-还在生我的气 对吧? -早知道就不来了
Maybe you shouldn't have come...
或许你不该来
..if you're gonna keep whining about every little cougar...
要是每次遇到攻击你的小美洲鹏…
..that attacks you,
就在那边抱她的话
Oh, what does this look like?
嗓 这看起来如何?
You making your own fire?
你要自己升火?
No, I'm making arrows, We're gonna need them,
不 我在做箭 我们会有需要的
-You still coming? -Yeah,
-你还会跟我一起来? -对
Yeah!
太好了
Yeah, You're my buddy, Yeah,
好 你真是我兄弟
You're saying we're gonna walk...
你是说我们继续走
First of all, why are you talking to me in that tone like I'm an idiot?
首先 你说话的语气 为什么好像把我当白汪?
-I knew it! This is incredible,
-我就知道 -太不可置信了
You still think the world just ends?
你还认为世界会有尽头吗?
Come on, admit it, The fruit man has the knowledge,
拜托 承认吧 这个水果人有大脑
Whoa, whoa, be careful,
小心皮
Did you learn a lot when you ate the fruit?
你吃禁果后真的知道很多事?
-That's not funny, -I'm not joking,
-不好笑 -没在开玩笑
Hope you're ready to bone some zeeb,
希望你准备好让斑马碍一下
People, More than one,
有人 不只一个人
Walking that way,
往那边走
You think? There's about a thousand footprints there,
你以为呢? 这里大概有一千个聊印
Two men, maybe three, A child, Or a small woman, maybe,
两个人 或许三个人 一个小孩 或是个子小的女人 或许…
What are you doing? You don't know where that's been,
你在做什么? 你不知道那是谁的大便
-l know where it's been, -Don't touch it,
-我知道是谁的 -别碰
Still warm, Almost hot in the center,
还是温的 中间还是热的
Looks like they had some nuts, Apples, maybe,
看来他们吃了点核果 或许还有蔷果
What are you doing?
你在做什么?
-Yep, apples, -What difference does it make?
-对 蔷果 -这有什么关系?
That doesn't help us to know that,
又不能帮助我们知道什么
You can tell if they ate some shit, There's a lot of shit in that shit,
要是他们吃大便 你或许会知道 大便里有很多大便
My mistake, this is bear poop,
我错了 这是能大便
What's that, though?
但那是什么?
This one's mine,
这只是我的
Tonight, we feast,
今晚 我们举办盛宴
We're gonna need some arrowheads,
我们需要箭头
This is where you die!
你的死期到了
Easy, easy,
慢点 慢点
He won't get far,
他和逃不远的
-Did you shoot my cow? -Oh, no,
-你射我的牛吗? -不是
Yes, Well, we're hunters,
对 我们是猎人
Well, he's a hunter, I'm a maker,
他是猎人 我是工匠
-A maker? -[ made this loincloth, l make arrows,
-工匠? -我会做善衣和箭
I've made a shelf unit for my hut,
还帮有自己的小屋做了架子
I welcome us to you,
我很高兴来到你们这里
-What do you do? -What does it look like?
-你们是做什么的? -看起来像什么?
-We're farmers, -Well, he's a farmer, I'm a herdsman,
-我们是农夫 -他是农夫 我是牧人
You're a suck is what you are,
你的工作烂透了
-My brother Cain, I'm called Abel, -You are called "suck,"
-他是我哥该隐 我叫埃布尔 -你是烂人
You're suckling up to God, You're a suckle-up,
对上帝来说你烂透了 你是个烂人
Somebody's upset because God looked on my sacrifice with favor,
有人生气是因为上帝重怜我的你品
"God looked upon my sacrifice with favor," 1 mean--
上帝重怜我的你品 我是说…
-Is he a total suck or what? -Hard to say, We just met,
-他真的很烂 对不对? -很难说 我们刚认识
Why are you bringing these guys init?
你为什么把他们扯进来? 他们什么都不知道
-They live ina tree, -Oh, see?
-他们住在树林里 -你看?
I mean, come on, You just gotta be so superior to everyone else,
拜托 你就是得比其他人厉害
No, but superior to-- Than you,
不 但是比你厉害
Superior-- Let's see how superior you are when I kick your ass,
厉害 等我打你时 看谁比较厉害
-Oh, yeah? -You want some of that?
-是吗? -你要比一场吗?
-Yes, do, -Guys,
-对 没错 -各位
-I'm right here, I'm right here, -No, come on,
-我就在这里 来啊 -不 拜托
No, This smug asshole insulted you, and I want him to take it back,
这个自大的混蛋侮怕了你 我要他尝溉代价
-We're not that insulted, -Why don't you make me?
-我们没被侮怕 -你逼我试试看
No, no, Boys, boys, You are brothers, Let's just relax...
不 两位 你们是兄弟 放轻松点
..and let's all just get some perspective
我们看远一点…
Yeah, Yeah, That's how we do it, That's how we do it, That's--
好 好 我们就要这么做 就要这么做…
-There are rules that we abide by, -Yeah, right,
-这就是我们的规撼 -对 没错
-Should we do something? -Just let them settle it,
-我们 该想想办法吗? -让他们自己解决
I tripped,
我跌倒了
Well, I guess that settles it,
我猜已经解决了
-What? -Nothing,
-什么? -没什么
It's-- He's all right, He's just-- He's resting,
他没事 他只是在睡觉
Well, he's tuckered out from the fight,
他打架打累了
Yeah, yeah, yeah, He's-- You know what?
对 对 你知道吗?
Let's cover him up with a little dirt and some straw...
我们用些王和稻草盖着他
..to keep him warm until he wakes up and...,
主他保持温暖 等他醒来…
Hey, Abel, what are you doing with my foot? Playing possum?
埃布尔 你对我的脚做了什么? 玩负饼游戏吗?
Hey, Oh, hey, stop it, He's choking me,
住手 他在的我
Stop it, Abel, Are you trying to choke me to death, Abel?
住手 埃布尔 你想的死我吗?
"Yes, Cain, lam," Come on, stop it!
"对 该隐 没错”拜托 住手
Self-defense, Clearly, Self-defense,
自我防卫 显然是自我防卫
What have I done?
我做了什么事?
What have I done again? What have I done some more?
我又做了什么事? 我又做了什么?
What have I continued to do?
我又继续做了什么?
Oh, guys, Guys, we're in some real trouble here,
各位 我们真的遇到麻烦了
What do you mean, "we''?
你说“我们”是什么意思?
I don't wanna play the blame game but you hit him,
我不是想推镍责任 不过是你打他的
No, no, no, There's two of you and there's one of me,
不 你们有两个人 我只有一个人
-You could have stopped me, -Didn't know you were gonna kill him,
-你们可以阻止我 -我不知道你要杀了他
-Are you calling me a murderer? -Did I say that?
-你说我是凶手吗? -我有说吗?
Yeah, you were holding a rock...
对 你拿着石头
..and he ran into it with his face repeatedly...
他一直用脸撞石头
..until he just couldn't pull through,
直到他再也醒不过来
-It was horseplay,
-这只是恶作剧 -是恶作剧
It was two horses playing,
这是两个人在恶作剧
One murders the other one...,
一个人杀了另一个人
Yeah, It's probably best if we didn't mention this accident to anyone,
我们别跟别人提这件意外比较好
Because, you know, people don't understand, and--
因为别人不会理解的 而且…
Who am I gonna tell?
我要下谁说?
I can't think of one who'd be interested,
我想不到有谁会有兴趣听
I'd only tell him and he's a witness as well,
我只会跟他说 他也是目击者
-Why even bring it up? -Okay,
-为什么要提这件事? -好
-It's like he killed himself, -Cry for help, if anything,
-他是自杀 -不然就是找人帮忙
All right, Good,
好 太好了
I like you guys, I do, I like you guys a lot, I do,
我喜欢你们 真的 我很喜欢你们 真的
Why don't you come over to my place for supper?
何不来我家吃晚餐?
-We already have dinner plans, -Damn,
-我们已经有晚餐计划了 -该死
Why don't you come over to my place for supper?
你们何不来我家吃晚餐?
We'll come over to your place for supper,
我们会去你家吃晚餐
-Just don't kill me, -No horseplay,
-别杀我就好 -不要恶作剧
What are these big, round things for?
这些又大又圆的东西是什么?
They're wheels, numbskull, They make the cart roll,
那是轮子 繁蛋 这样车子才会跑
feel like a bird,
我觉得自己好像小乌
Bring it forth,
往前走
Hello,
你好
I'm gonna yak,
我快吐了
-Let me get your hair, -That was too fast,
-我帮你撩头发 -太快了
Cain, I ask you again, where is thy brother Abel?
该隐 我再问你一次 你第埃布尔呢?
I don't know, I haven't really seen him at all,
我不知道 我没看到他
Have you-- You guys..., You guys haven't seen him, have you?
你们…你们有看到他吗?
-Don't know who you're talking about, -What's his name?
-我不知道你在说什么 -他叫什么?
-Sure he's out there somewhere... -l haven't seen anybody anywhere,
-他一定在某个地方 -我没看到任何人
Never had the pleasure, Sure he's in the prime of his life,
没机会见到他 他一定很年轻力壮
This is good soup, Really good,
这汤真好喝 真棒
Lilith said she saw you in the field with him,
你妹妹 莉莉英说看到你和他在田地上
Oh, man, this bread is good,
老兄 这面包真棒
Oh, really? That-- Oh, yeah, No, that was yesterday, right,
真的吗? 没错 那是昨天的事
No, this day, She said you both made offerings,
不 今天 她说你们都拿出祭品了
-Oh, that was Boaz, Yeah, -No,
-那是波阿斯 对 -不是
-Japheth, It was Japheth,
-雅弗 是雅弗
-Enoch, -No,
-以诺 -不是
-I'm sure it was Gilgamesh,
-我确定是吉尔格美斯
-Ishmael, -No,
-以实玛利 -不是
-Ezidia?
-爱弯达亚?
-Jennifer? -No,
-珍妮弗? -不是
Now I'm remembering correctly, It was Tishbaven,
现在我想起来了 确实是提希巴文
It was you, She said it looked like you were arguing,
是你 她说你们看来像在吵架
Yeah, well, let's be honest, Lilith is a lying bitch,
对 说实话好了 莉莉英是个爱说谎的贱人
Look, I mean, we're brothers, We're gonna argue, it's human nature,
我们是兄弟 都会吵架的 这是人的天性
-Show me the perfect family, -His flock goes untended in the field,
-哪有完美的家庭 -他的牡畜都没人管
Okay, look, Enough, Am I his keeper?
好 听着 够了 我是他的监护人吗?
I mean, just get off my back, Father,
别找我麻烦了 老和爸
I wish you were dead too, Even though Abel's not dead at all,
但愿你也去死 虽然埃布尔根本没死
I fear the worst for Abel, I'm sorely vexed,
我很担心埃布尔 我有很不好的感觉
You're welcome to spend this night with us,
欢迎两位留下来过夜
You may lay with my daughter Lilith,
你可以和我女儿莉莉英一起睡
She is without a husband...
她没有先生
..and as the Lord said, "Be fruitful and multiply,"
而且如上帝所言 要多子多和孙
What about me?
那我呢?
You may share the bed of my son Seth,
你可以和我儿子塞特一起睡
-Thanks, Papa, -Yeah, there you go,
-和爸 谢谢 -走吧
Your brother Seth is an interesting guy,
你弟弟赛特真的非常有趣
Did you know he can put his own penis in his mouth?
你知道他可以把 自己的鸡鸡放进自己嘴里吗?
I did not know that,
我不知道
It's been a great sleepover...
昨晚过得很好
..and thank you for the gruel and the garb,
谢谢你的粥和衣服
Cain,
该隐
-Where's everybody going? -To look for thy brother Abel,
-大家去哪里了? -去找你弟埃布尔
-Good luck, -What?
-祝他们好运 -什么?
I said, good luck, Father, I'm really worried about him,
我说祝他们好运 和爸 我真的很担心他
You're not coming?
你不去吗?
I'm just gonna stay here and finish toiling...
我要待在这里把车工做完
-..and then we'll be right behind you, -Good,
-然后我们马上就去找你 -很好
Hey, I'm heading to the coast, You guys should come with me,
我要去海边 你们应该跟我走
They're gonna try to blame this whole Abel-killing business on you,
我有预感他们要把埃布尔死亡事件 全都归欠于你们
-Why blame it on us? -When they find him...
-为什么要怪我们? -因为等他们找到他
..and see his head, they're gonna start pointing fingers, You're drifters,
看到他的头被打烂了 他们就会找凶手 你们是流浪汉
They're gonna put two and two together,
他们会两两分组
Now stop asking so many questions and let's go, Go, go, go,
别问那么多问题 我们走了 快…
Cain, After him,
该隐 去找他
-They're gaining on us, -They're getting away,
-他们找到我们了 -他们要逃了
-Eat my dust, Father, -This is really too fast,
-吃灰吧 老爸 -这真的太快了
-Oh, no, no, -Hold tight, Hold tight,
-不 -抓紧 抓紧了
No, No! Damn you, Cain,
不 该死 该隐
Who's in God's favor now, Father?
神现在站在谁那边 老爸?
What are the odds of that? Hey, am I lucky or what?
那机牵是多少? 我是不是很幸运?
Your head's smoking,
你的头在置烟
Hey, it didn't leave a mark, did it?
没留下疤痕 对不对?
Just a pink, red hole,
只是有个粉红.… 红色的洞
-Your bangs are gonna cover it, -All right, Whatever,
-你的头带可以盖住 -好 管他的
This is the biggest place I've ever seen,
这是我见过最大的地方
It's called a town, Just act normal,
这叫做城市 行为正常点
-Hi, -Hello, Greetings, seafarer,
-你好 -你好 船员
-That's not normal, -Hello,
-那不叫正常 -你好
Would you stop saying hi to everybody? It's annoying,
你别一直跟别人打招呼 很烦人耶
All right, this is a market, Over there is a Build-A-Bear,
好 这里是市场 这里是能工作室
That's a really good container store, Oh, this place has killer hemp,
那家店卖的锥子很棒 这里还有杀手大麻
-Yes, please, -Next up is an unusual item,
-麻烦你 -下一项很罕见
-He's big, He's strong, -It's Marlak,
-他又大又强壮 -是马拉
Oh, do not worry, He is not fighting, he is having fun,
别担心 他不是在打架 只是在玩
Okay, maybe he's little bit depressed,
好 或许他有点怖孝
Maya and Eema,
玛雅和伊玛
-Zed, -Eema,
-柴德 -伊玛
-Hi, -Hi, Hi, Gosh,
-你好 -你好 老天
What happened? How did you get here?
怎么了? 你们怎么会来这里?
After the fire that you started, the hill tribes raided the village,
你族了火之后 山上的部落 占领了我们的部落
They held us captive...
他们把我们抓起来
So it's such a coincidence to run into you guys like this here,
像这样遇到你们还真巧
-You think it's a coincidence? -What do you think?
-你还认为这是巧合? -不然呢?
I'm not sure, but I'm beginning to think that everything happens for a reason,
我不确定 但我开始认为 发生这一切都是有原因的
God wanted me to have knowledge of good and evil,
上帝要我拥有分状善恶的知识
-Why would he want that? -Why are we assuming God's a he?
-他为什么要那样? -为什么认为上帝是男的?
I don't know what to say to that,
我不知道该怎么回答
You kidding?
开玩笑吗?
Anyway, don't you guys see what I'm saying?
无论如何 你们不懂我说的话吗?
Why would he choose you?
他为什么选择你?
Why wouldn't he choose someone stronger?
为什么不选个强壮点的? 像马拉
Chosen doesn't have to be strong, I'm big like this,
上帝所选的人不一定是强者 我这里很大
-You have a fat face, -My brain, It's enormous,
-你有张胖脸 -不是脸 是头脑 大脑
I'm smarter than you are, I don't talk as much,
我比你们聪明 只是没说出来
I'm the smartest guy in the village,
我是村里最聪明的人
I'm the smartest guy that was in the village,
我才是村里最聪明的人
Excuse me, you are interested in some slaves?
打扰一下 你对奴隶有兴趣吗?
Yes,
是的
-This one looks pretty good, -And her little friend, Very good,
-这个看起来不错 -她的小朋友也非常好
-Just how I like them, “Hey,
-我喜欢它们 一哇 ov
So how do we do this if we want them?
如果我们要她们 该怎么做?
You have money?
你有钱吗?
That depends on what you mean by money,
看你对钱的定义是什么
Excuse me, Perhaps I could be of some help here,
打扰一下 或许我能帮点忙
You guys, let me deal with this guy, see if I can work out a deal,
你们让我和这家伙谈 看看我能不能谈得成
What happened to your forehead?
你前额怎么了?
I didn't murder my brother, I didn't,
我没杀我弟 我没有
All right, I'm just gonna--
好 我只是要…
We're gonna get you out of this, You trust me?
我们会救出你们的 你相信我吗?
-[ want to trust you, -Fair enough,
-我很起相信你 -这就够了
Next up is a twofer, It is two for price of one,
下一项半价优待 买一送一
Have a great vacation,
度假愉快
Never trusted that guy,
绝对不能相信那家伙
Because he murdered his brother with a rock?
因为他用石头杀了他弟?
Is that why you didn't trust him? You got great instincts,
所以你不相信他? 你的直觉真准
Sorry, do you think you could move your hands, please?
对不起 你的手可以移开一点吗?
Yeah,
可以
-Sorry, -Thank you,
-对不起 -谢谢
Enmebaragesi, can you move that way a little bit? We're crowded back here,
恩米巴拉格西 你能过去一点吗? 我们这边很挤
Oh, yeah, no problem, How's that?
好 没问题 现在怎么样?
.. 1 blame myself for everything that's happened,
这一切都是我的错
-Yeah, So does everybody else, -Stay away from my woman,
-对 每个人都这么想 -离我的女人远一点
Not gonna be possible, Marlak,
不可能的 马拉
She's not your woman, You can't own people,
她不是你的女人 你不能拥有任何人
That's it, -What?
-我受够了 -什么?
-I'm gonna kill you! -"I'm gonna kill you,"
-我要宰了你! - "我要宰了你”
You always say, "I'm gonna kill you" and you never do,
你每次都说“我要宰了你 从来没做到
Be still, Don't make me come in there,
不要乱动 别逼我进去里面
I'd like to see you try,
我很想看你试试看
Take the slaves!
抢走奴隶
Eema, run like a cougar is chasing you,
伊玛 假装豹在追你 快跑
-Zed! -Eema,
-柴德 -伊玛
Come here, you two,
过来 你们两个
Sir, shall we pursue the slaves?
长官 我们要追奴隶吗?
Let the desert have them, They won't get far,
让沙漠制服他们 他们跑不远的
Yes, sir,
是 长官
-Orders, sir? -Tend to the slaves,
-长官 有命令吗? -告诉奴录们
-We leave for Sodom before daybreak, -Yes, sir,
-我们黎明前出发至所多玛 -是 长官
I wonder who they are,
不知道他们是谁
Their hats are really great, aren't they?
他们的帽子真棒 对不对?
Their hats?
他们的蛋子?
When that guy cut the other guy's head off...
当那家伏天下其他人的头
.. 1 wasn't thinking about what a great hat,
我才不会想到什么帽子
It wasn't my very first thought, but I'd be lying if I said it wasn't up there,
我不是先想到这个 但要是说我没想到 那就是说谎
I'm just saying, if l can snag one, I'm going to,
我只是想设法弄到一顶
Now I just have to figure out a way to rescue Maya and Eema,
现在我得先想办法救出玛雅和伊玛
How are we gonna rescue them? These guys are killers,
我们要怎么救她们? 这些家伙是杀手
Even killers have to sleep sometime,
就算是杀手也要睡觉
That was refreshing,
精神好多了
Shit!
可恶
They're gone,
他们不见了
Now where do we go?
我们现在要去哪里?
They said they were going to Sodom, We're going to Sodom,
他们说要去所多玛 我们也去所多玛
I think I have sand in my ass, but there's no way of knowing for sure,
我觉得我屁股里有沙子 不过也没办法确定
I'll take a look in it when we get to Sodom,
等我们到所多玛再帮你看看
We making a burnt offering or something?
我们该弄些祭品吗?
Yes, Isaac, As God has commanded me,
对 艾萨克 如神的指令
But I don't see the sheep anywhere,
但我没看到有羊
The Lord, The Lord shall provide the sheep, my son,
主 主会给我们羊 吾儿
What is this? Is this some sort of magic trick?
怎么了? 你要变魔术吗?
In a way, In a way,
算是 算是
If this is because I didn't clean up my tent, I'm sorry,
如果这是因为我没打扫帐雍 我道歉
I'll do it right when I get home,
等我回家我马上扫
Oh, Dad, why are you doing this?
答 你为什么这么做?
The Lord has spoken unto me, Isaac, and I must obey him,
艾萨克 主对我下了指示 我必须遵从他
If the Lord told you to jump off a cliff, would you do it?
要是主叫你跳下悬崖 你也会跳吗?
-Forgive me, Isaac, -My God,
-艾萨克 原谅我 -老天
Stop! What are you doing with that kid?
住手 你要对那孩子做什么?
-Nothing, -Nothing?
-没什么 -没什么?
This is my son, sir, We were playing a game,
这是我儿子 我们在玩游戏
All right? It's called Burny Burny Cut Cut,
好吗? 这叫烧烧切切
You weren't, You were gonna kill him,
才不是 你要杀了他
I was not going to kill him, I was going to sacrifice him,
我不是要杀他 我是拿他当妹品
-There is a tremendous difference, -Not to him,
-这有很大的差异 -对他来说都一样
-Aye, Aye, verily, thou art, -Verily, Yea,
-是 此话当真? -的确 是的
Thou were sent by the Eternal One to stay my hand,
注为永恒者派来阻挡我的手
-All of that, This is Isaac,
-没错 -这是艾萨克
And Iam Abraham, the son of Terah of the House of Nahor,
我叫亚伯拉罕 拿航家 他拉之子
We were two doors down from Nahor, We were Nahor's neighbors,
我们和拿葛家隔两户 我们是拿划的邻居
And Il am Zed, son of Zero,
我叫柴德 柴火之子
And this is Oh, son of Ooh from the House of Sticks and Dung,
他叫欧仔 欧之子 来自棒类家族
Come, Come, my friends,
来 来 我的朋友
We are the Hebrews,
我们是希伯来人
A righteous people, but not very good at sports,
正直的民族 但很不擅长运动
This way, friends, Come,
这边走 朋友 来
Brothers, brothers,
兄弟们
.. for staying my hand on the mountain this very day,
在今天这个非常的日子里 在山上拉住了我的手
Praise be to God, hallowed be his name,
赞美上帝 颂扬他的名
And let us also praise him...
我们也赞美他
.. for the bounty which he hath bestowed unto us,
慷慨赠与我们的一切
He hath increased our wealth...
他让我们更富有
..and blessed us with--
而且祝福我们…
Thanks, Thank you, A lot of loving things,
谢谢 谢谢你 多么好的东西
-Kind loving kindness, -Yeah,
-谢谢你们的仁感 -对
Friends, whence comest thou?
朋友 从何而来?
..the Cities of the Plain, from Sodom and Gomorrah,
平原的各城 而是所多玛与娥摩拉
-Heard of them, never been there, -Are they nice?
-听说过 没去过 -很棒吗?
“Are they nice?"
很棒吗?
They have been cursed for all time by the Lord thy God...
那里被上帝诅咒许久
-..for their abominations, -I did not know that,
-因为他们的罪恶 -我不知道
They worship idols and they bow down before false gods,
他们尝拜偶像 而且在其他伪神前屎膝
-Abdominal, -It's the worst,
-真可恶 -很碍糕
The men of that city are weak and soft...
那里的人软弱无用
..fat with rich food, intoxicated by strong drink,
吃太多而发胖 因喝酒而中毒
I'm not hearing the bad part,
我没听到有什么不好的地方
The women are whores,
女人都是妓女
Their shameless lust knows no bounds,
他们无耶 不知道节制
They flaunt their flesh...
他们炉砍他们的肉体
..and any man may have knowledge of them whenever he so chooseth,
任何认识他们的男人 只要愿意就能上床
Which one of the two cities has the most whores?
哪个城市的妓女最多?
Just so we know to stay away from that one especially,
我们要知道 才能特别避开那里
Walk you not the path of Sodom,
注不可行菲恶之道
For the Lord thy God has said unto me...
上帝曾对得言
..that he shall send a holy fire to destroy that city...
他将询圣火氛毁该城
..and all who dwell within for their iniquity,
所有那恶之人也将被毁灭
He shall smite them,
他将惩罚他们
Them, and all of their seed,
他们 与他们的子襄
So when do you think this smiting's gonna go down?
你觉得什么时候会开始惩罚?
-Because we have some friends there, -Their fate is sealed,
-因为我们在那里有朋友 -他们的命运已定
But for my faith and devotion...
但我的信仰与谨诚
..that self-same God...
唯一真主…
..has promised unto me the whole of this land,
已应允我这片土地
From the Heights of Golan in the north to the Sinai in the south,
从北方的及兰高地到南方的西泰
From the river of Jordan to the great sea,
从约旦河到大海
-This is all your land? -For all of eternity,
-这都是你的地? -直到永远
We're at war with someone every other day,
我们每天都在和别人打侈
Excuse me, I and my kinsmen have vanquished our enemies...
抱欢 我和我的家族 已征服我们的敌人
..by the mighty hand of God, blessed be he
藉由全能的上帝之手 上帝祝福
Do you have any idea where we're going?
你知道我们要去哪里吗?
Going to Sodom, We have to save Maya and Eema,
去所多玛 我们要去救玛雅和伊玛
He said that God was gonna smite Sodom with holy fire,
他说上帝要用圣火挫席所多玛
God also told him to chop off the tip of his dick,
上帝也叫他把小弟弟顶端切下来
Dad, no! No! No!
爸 不要 不要
So listen, I've been thinking, what constitutes the tip of the penis?
听着 我想过了 阳具顶端是什么?
Because his definition might not be the same as mine,
因为他的定义可能和我的不一样
-What if the tip is your favorite part? -The tip is your only part,
-如果顶端是你最喜欢的部分呢? -你只有顶端
Come out here,
出来
Hey, you caught me, Guilty,
你还到我了
What are you doing here?
你来这里做什么?
-I'm gonna come, -You don't know where we're going,
-我要跟你们一起走 -你又不知道我们要去哪里
-You're going to Sodom, right? -No,
-你们要去所多玛 对吗? -不是
How stupid you think I am? You've had a boner for Sodom...
你以为我有多策? 我爸提到所多玛后
..since my dad mentioned it, If l take you, get me some wine,
你的小弟弟就有反应了 要是我带你去 就给我喝酒
Aren't you a bit young?
你不会太年轻吗?
Do you like hanging out with this little girl?
你想和这小女孩鬼混?
The devil's playground, where the sinners are winners,
恶魔的游乐园 在那里罪人当家做主
Me and my boys sneak in here on the weekends sometimes,
我和我朋友周末有时候会渔来这里
Pick up on the babes, drink some wine, smoke some herb,
挑几个马子 喝几杯酒 抽几根烟
-Shouldn't be smoking either, -Thanks a lot, Grandpa,
-你不该抽烟的 -区区 谢了
I've been smoking for four harvests now, so I think I'm good,
我已经抽四年了 我想我没问题
These doors are enormous,
这门还真大
-It looks like they're not open, so-- -You just gotta knock,
-看来没开 所以… -你只要敲门就好
-They let me in all the time, -Yeah, knock,
-他们都会让我进去 -去敲门
-Why don't you knock? -You knock,
-你为什么不? -你吉
-What if we're waking somebody? -Eema and Maya might be in there,
-要是我们吵醒别人怎么办? -伊玛和玛雅可能在里面
I gave them our word we'd rescue them,
我说过我们会救她们
I want to get my dicky sticky,
我想我的小弟弟再兴奋些
-Halt, Halt, -Get help, Tell your father,
-等等 -去求救 跟你区说
Like I'm gonna tell my father I came with you guys to Sodom,
难道我会告诉我爸 我跟你们来所多玛?
So long, suckers,
再见了 策蛋
I kind of get why his dad wanted to kill him,
我大概知道他和苑为什么想杀他了
Get in,
进去
-What's this, then? -They were banging on the gate,
-怎么回事? -他们在撞门
-Hebrews from the look of them, -Well, we're not really Hebrews,
-看起来像希伯来人 -我们其实不是希伯来人
We are Hebrews?
我们是希伯来人?
I get it, No talking,
我慌了 不准说话
-Should we wake the commander? -Oh, no,
-要叫醒指挥官吗? -不
Don't want to wake the commander, He gets mean when you wake him,
别叫醒指挥官 他被吵醒时会变得很刻薄
Meaner than this?
比这还刻薄?
Let go of his titty,
放开他的乳头
Yeah, Okay, All right, good one,
对 好了 好了 这招厉害
What the bloody hell is going on out there?
外面到底是怎么回事?
Who screamed? Sounded like a woman,
谁在夫叫? 听起来和娘们一样
But you don't look like a woman, You wanna kiss me?
不过你不像女人 你想亲我吗?
Like in a romantic way?
浪漫的那种吻吗?
By tomorrow morning, you'll wish you hadn't been born,
到明天早上 你会希望你没出生过
-l already feel that way right now, -Yeah,
-我现在已经有那种感觉了 -是的
Why don't you pick on someone your own size?
为什么不找个 和你身材一样的人刁难?
Because that I would pay to see, You versus a guy your size,
因为我愿意花钱 看你和身材一样的人对打
Give me my stick,
把我的棒子给我
Bumpy, You got a smoother one?
凹四西西的 有没有平一点的?
Yeah,
没错
Turn around and put your hands on the table,
转过去 把手放到桌上
Now!
快
I'll take that kiss now,
我愿意亲你了
-We'll start with the fat one, -Relatively fat, l mean...,
-从胖子开始 -我只是相对较胖
-Welcome to Sodom, -Hey, I want a piece of that,
-欢迎来到所多玛 -我也要玩
-Cain? -You know them?
-该隐? -你认识他们?
Brothers,
兄弟
I missed you so much, Oh, you guys, Promise you'll never leave me again,
我好想你们 你们两个 答应我 你们不会再离开我
-This is amazing, -And this is a Monday,
-真是太神奇了 -对 今天星期一
You should see this place ona Thursday,
你该看看这里星期四的样子
-Because Thursday's the new Friday, -Well, thanks for saving us,
-因为星期四是新的星期五 -谢谢你救了我们
-What are you gonna do to us now? -Excuse me? Do I detect a tone here?
-你现在要对我们做什么? -说什么?3 有人不商兴吗?
You did sell us into slavery,
你确实有把我们卖给奴录贩啊
Hold a grudge much? That was, like, a fortnight ago,
还在记优? 那是两星期前的事了
It was less than a fortnight, Half a fortnight,
还不到两个礼拜 才一个礼拜
-It was a sevennight, -Oh, give me a break,
-是七个晚上 -饶了我吧
I was dealing with the death...
我还要面对很亲近的…
..0f a close, personal family member and I needed some space,
家人死亡的事实 我需要点空间
But hey, now I realize that you guys are like my real brothers,
不过现在我知道 你们就像我的亲生兄弟一样
And it's so rare to have a brother that you love and don't wanna kill,
有个你很爱 但不想杀他的兄弟 真的很难得
Hey, who's hungry?
谁俄了?
-I'm hungry, -Don't kill me,
-我俄了 -别杀我
Yeah? Okay,
是吗? 好
Excuse me, I was...,
打扰一下 我…
Yeah, that's two for flinching, Hey, let's go,
好 你退了两步 快一点
Here, Now we're even,
给你们 现在我们拉平了
Check out the woman across the way, She's looking at us,
你看对面那个女人 她在看我们
She's totally eye-knowing us with her eyes right now,
她正用她的眼神勾引我们
If you guys are gonna stay here, you should join the guard, ()
如果你们要待在这里 就要加入敬卫的行列
-Hey! -Hey, hey what, hey? Huh? Yeah,
-哩? 本 -嘿什么嘿?
I mean, the pay's not great but the perks, tons of them,
薪水不是很好 不过津贴 让你荷包满满
I'm telling you, it's the only way to go, Come on, let's go talk to the sergeant,
我跟你说 这是唯一的方法 快点 我们去找警卫官恋
-Let's go, -Hurry now,
-我们走 -快点
This is great, How do I look?
太棒了 我看起来如何?
I can't see, This is too big on me, I wonder if I can get a smaller size,
我看不到了 这太大了 不知道有没有小一点的
Yeah, someone's gotta be the hat person around here,
管巾子的人应该在附近
-Find a..., -Excuse me,
一去找… -打扰一下
Hey, my helmet is way too big for me, It looks really silly,
我的头盔太大了 看起来真的很蠢
-Think I can get a smaller one? -Line up!
-有没有小一点的? -列队
-What are you doing? In the line, -Wait, he's not...,
-你在做什么? 进队伍去 -等等 他不是…
In the line, Face forward in the line,
进队伍去 面向前
-Guys, Guys? - don't know where to...,
-各位 -我不知道去哪里.…
-Guys, -You too!
-你也是
-Find a hole, you stupid bastards,
-各位 -找个洞 你这策蛋
-It's kind of obvious, isn't it? -Not to me,
-很简单 对不对?
Soldiers, Present arms,
士兵 亮出武器
I never got a sword, l only got the holder,
我没拿到剑 只有剑鞘
I didn't know that that's what it was for,
我不知道那是做什么的
-So this is it? We just walk around? -Yeah, pretty much,
-就这样? 走来走去就好? -对 差不多
Just look for troublemakers,
找制造麻烦的人
If you see a thief or a pickpocket, we'll slap them around a little bit,
要是你看到小偷或扒手 就把他们痛打一顿
Maybe cut off a finger, you know, or tip of the nose sometimes,
或许切下一根指头 有时候切鼻子
Lower lip, Just anything you can grab and slice in one fluid motion,
下嘴唇 只要能用流畅的动作 抓起来切掉的都可以
It seems kind of harsh,
听起来很严厉
Hey, just remember it's the palace that pays us, not the people, Come on,
只要记得 是皇宫付钱给我们 不是人民 快点
Feed us!
咀我们吃饭
Six sacrifices in the last 10 days and still no rain,
过去十天献祭了六次 还是不下雨
Majesty, there's talk of revolution in the streets,
陛下 街上兴起改革声浪
Oil and grain are scarce, prices are high,
油和谷物都缺货了 价格峰涨
Starving peasants are pouring into the city in search of food,
饥钱的农民涌入城市寻找食物
We could actually have a riot on our hands,
我们可能会发生暴动
Poverty has a bitter taste, but it is a flavor they are born to,
贫穷人是爱抱怨 但他们天生如此
It is the will of the gods, What do the entrails predict?
这是神的细意 内脏占下结果如何?
Well, the liver is streaked with gray, which is not a good sign...
肝脏有灰色条纹 这不是好迹象
..but his poor rectum is absolutely pulverized...
但他的直肠已经完全负环
..Which is not unusual for a sheep in this region,
这对这区的羊来说很不寻常
The genitals are enormous,
生殖器非常巨大
That's of no significance, I'm just commenting,
这没有特别意义 我只是做个评论
If you do look at this intestine...
如果你看看这个肠子
. his large intestine is arranged in an arc...
他的大肠呈现一个狐型
..then the two massive balls of the sheep are like eyes,
而这两颗巨大的羊墨九就像腿睛
What does it mean?
什么意思?
Well, could mean a surprise visit from a former friend or sweetheart,
可能表示以前的朋友或爱人 会有意外的拜访
Or that you're going ona long sea voyage,
或是你将进行长途的海上旅程
Could l come? I've never been on a boat,
我能芙吗? 我没上过船
How did you become high priest?
你怎么成为最高祭司的?
I'm your brother-in-law,
我是你太太的哥哥
Perhaps it's not time
或许还不是换新祭司的时候
Let that be a warning to you,
那是个警告
Next time, I shall hurl a lightning bolt right in your face,
下次 我会朝你的脸射出一道闪电
Or a fireball,
或是火球
And you know what's the best part about Sodom? The sodomy,
你知道所多玛最棒的是什么吗? 鸡奸
You guys are in for a treat,
我请你们去
Down,
欢下
Did you see that girl?
你看到那女生了吗?
That was Princess Inanna,
那是伊南娜公主
She's totally hot, Don't even think about it,
她超辣 但想都不要想
Why not?
为什么?
Why? Because she's royalty and you're a caveman,
为什么? 因为她是皇室 你只是个野变人
Where's everybody going?
大家要去哪里?
To the temple, You guys have to see this,
去神庙 你们一定要来看看
-Will she be there? -Yeah, everyone'll be there,
-她也会去吗? -对 大家都会去
There she is,
她在那里
The princess isn't eating,
公主不吃东西
I find it hard to eat when so many are hungry,
这么多人处于饥俄 我食不下咽
-You can't keep starving yourself, -Why not?
-你不能一直扭俄 -为什么不行?
Everybody else is starving, Present company excluded,
其他人都在握俄 现在在我旁边的人除外
You may be my stepdaughter, but these are dangerous times...
你是我的继女 但现在时机危急
-..and those are dangerous words, -Whatever,
-你的话也很危险 -随便只
Hi,
骑
Yeah,
姥
-What's happening? -They're picking a virgin,
-怎么了? -他们要挑个处女
Oh, please, If you're a virgin, then I'm a fuzzy little gerbil,
拜托 如果你是处女 那我就是沙鼠
Back to the whorehouse with you, Quick as a bunny, There you go,
请你回你的妓院去 快一点 再见
What do they need a virgin for?
他们要处女做什么?
-To throw her in the fire, Are you new? -What? Why?
-把她委进火里 你新来的吗? -什么? 为什么?
An offering to the gods,
献绘上帝
-Are you serious? -There's a famine going on...
-真的? -现在有饥荒
..50 if we make a good enough sacrifice...
所以如果我们的祭品够好
..then the gods give us rain, You get rain, you get harvest...
天神就会赐给我们雨水 有了雨水才有收获
..you get harvest, you get food, You know what food is?
有了收获才有食物 你知道什么是食物 对吗?
Yeah, you know food,
对 你知道食物
So they're gonna throw a virgin into the fire so that it rains?
所以他们把处女丢进火里 就会下十了吗?
My 6-year-old knows,
我六岁的小孩都知道
I didn't think it was anything related to--
我没想到
Yeah, yeah, "I didn't think, I didn't think,"
对 对 "我没想、我没想"
It's the gods and it comes from virgins being burned,
是从上帝和被烧死的处女 那里来的
Did I do something to offend you?
我做了什么冒犯你的事吗?
I come here, I get a great seat at the sacrifice, and you're ruining it,
我来这里占了个看献祭的好位置 你却毁了它
Seems like a waste of a perfectly good virgin to me,
在我看来 这是在浪费超棒的处女
Hey, guys? I'm trying to enjoy the sacrifice with my family,
两位? 我想和我的家人 一起观看献祭
Do you mind? Do you mind?
你介意吗? 你介意吗?
For the love of the gods...
为了表达对众神的爱
..we commit this fair maiden...
我们将这位美丽的女人
..to Moloch's holy fire,
献给摩洛的圣火
These virgins, it's always a girl?
处女一定都是女生吗?
I'm really happy for her, She was always the runner-up,
我真的很为她高兴 她一直都是第二名
True success story,
真正的成功故事
My lord, the princess wishes to see you,
大人 公主想见你
Me? What about my friend?
我? 那我朋友呢?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, The three of us are like a pair,
对 我们三个就像是一对的
No, not you, The two of you, follow me,
不 你不行 你们两个跟我来
Great,
太好了
-I'll try to put a good word in for you, -Yeah, do,
-我会试着帮你说话 -好 一定要
If we never, ever see you again, it's not because we're avoiding you,
要是我们再也见不到你 绝不是因为我们避着你
Don't forget about me,
别忘了我
This is Zaftig, the eunuch, You, go with him,
这是太监赛夫提 你跟他走
Oh, can't I go with him?
我不能焉他走吗?
-Why? Is he your lover? -No, we're just friends,
-为什么? 他是你的爱人吗? -不 我们只是朋友
That would be weird, We're both guys,
真奇怪 我们都是男生
-Come with me, -What do you do?
-跟我来 -你是做什么的?
I've been a palace eunuch since I was 9 years old,
我九岁就进宫做太监
-How would I become a eunuch? -They cut off your testicles,
-我要怎样才能成为太监? -他们会切掉你的别九
Why all the genital mutilation?
为什么都要切掉生殖器?
Well, you get to keep them, l always keep mine close at hand,
你可以保留他们 我就一直留着我的在身边
Would you like to see?
你想看看吗?
No,
不想
Can I ask your opinion?
我能请教你的意见吗?
What do you think? Ponytail or no ponytail?
你有什么想法? 要不要有马尾?
-I don't know and I really don't care, -Okay, I just wanted to know...
-我不知道 我也不在乎 -好 我只是想知道
..What the ladies of Sodom were into nowadays, but...,
所多玛的小姐们 现在喜欢什么 可是.…
It's more of a hair-down kind of scene, I'd say,
比较适合把头发放下来
Hi,
骑
Be sure to try the fruit,
一定要试试水果
Maya, What are you doing here?
玛雅 你在这里做什么?
Okay, I'm still alive, thank you for asking...
好 我还活着 谢谢你的问候
..and I'm still a slave,
而且我还是个奴隶
I was coming to rescue you, Really, That's why we were here,
我本来是要来救你的 真的 所以我们才来这里
-We were gonna find you, -Yeah?
-我们本来要来找你的 -是吗?
I was just--
我只是…
-You were just chosen again, -l was,
-当然 你又被上帝选上了 -本来就是
I would love to join you at this orgy, but I can't...
我想加入你狂欢的行为 但我不能
.. because I have to go be a slave, and I don't get any breaks,
因为我得去当奴隶了 而且我不能休息
And the princess has crabs,
还有 公主有阴虱
Oh, yes, it's steamy,
好 真是热情
God, that's realistic,
老天 做得真像
Watch it, jerk,
小心点 混蛋
Areal woman, that's...,
真的女人 真是…
Ter, Mister, Awkward,
先生 先生 真怪
Good concentration,
定力真好
You're good, You're real good,
你真行 真的很行
-Oh? Is that you? -I'm not supposed to talk, I'm a statue,
-吗 是你吗? -我不该说话 我是雕像
-Yeah, you look so gold, -It's all the gold paint,
-对 你好人金 -都是金漆
-How's it going? -It's going great,
一怎么样? -非常好
I just had my entire body painted by a fat guy with no balls,
我刚被一个没蛋蛋的胖子 涂了一身的油漆
-Oh, how did that go? -He was extremely thorough,
-怎么漆的? -他漆得非常彻底
-How's it going with you? -Not bad,
-你好吗? -不差
Just had a little rub and scrub, Now I'm up for some grub,
只有一点探伤和挫伤 但我现在要举到甜头了
-Sounds luxurious, “Hey,
-听起来好淫荡 一哇 ov
You remember that woman who brought us in with the face dress?
你记得带着面罩 带我们进来的那个女生吗?
That was Maya, She's working here now and she looks great,
那是玛雅 她在这里工作 而且气色很好
-Kind of mad at me, though, -And there's Eema,
-不过有点生我的气 -伊玛在那里
Come here, wench,
过来 荡妇
Let me have a look what's up that skirt,
我看看裙子怎么了
-I'm sorry, it was an accident, -It was no accident,
-对不起 这是意外 -这不是意外
Hey, You, Slave girl, I told you to fetch me more wine,
你 奴隶 我叫你再去拿酒给我
-Apologize to this officer now, -I'm sorry,
-快球这个官员道歉 -对不起
Good, Now go fetch, Wait over there by the skinny statue,
很好 快去拿酒 在那个瘦铜像旁等我
I'll deal with you later, Go!
我晚点再找你算账 快去
Slaves, What are you gonna do?
奶录 你能拿他们怎么办?
Wait a minute,
等一等
Don't I know you?
我认识你吗?
-What are you, crazy? -I will not serve these people,
-你疯了吗? -我才不要服侍这些人
-I'd rather die, -Keep it up, You will,
-我宁愿死掉 -继续这样你就会死掉
Have you joined them?
你在这干嘛? 你加入他们了?
[haven't joined anything, I'm not having fun,
我没加入什么 我也不觉得开心
I'm just checking it out, A lot to learn here,
我只是去察看 这里有很多事要学
-What, human sacrifice? -No, No human sacrifices,
-什么? 人体献祭? -不 不要人体献你
I've been chosen to do something great,
我想我被上帝选来做些好事
Yeah, here we go,
对 又来了
I'm pretty sure it's not hunting pigs and weaving baskets,
我很确定不是猫猪或编篮子
-Oh? -Hello, Maya,
-是吗? -玛雅你好
She wants to see you, Now,
她想见你 现在
Don't think I'm interested in her,
别以为我对她有兴趣
-Whyever would I think that? -It's part of my plan,
-我为什么要那么想? -那是我计划的一部分
-The princess awaits you, -And I await her,
-公主在等你 -我也在等她
You two, await me, Stay out of trouble, Stay gold,
你们两个 等我 别车麻烦 继续当金人
He has no idea what he's doing, does he?
他不知道他在做什么 对不对?
-It's nice to see you like this, -It's nice to see you too,
-很高兴在这场合看到你 -我也很高兴看到你
We should do something, When do you get off?
我们可以找点事做 你什么时候下班?
-Never, I'm a slave, -Oh, yeah, of course,
-永远不会下班 我是奴隶 -对 当然了
Slave girl, bring me a towel,
奴录 把毛中给我
Yeah, I should go be a slave,
对 我该去当奴录了
I'm gonna strike a specific pose, I guess,
我要想个特别的姿势了
-Okay, -I love you,
-好 -我爱你
You there, Golden boy, Come here,
你 金男孩 过来
Rub me with oil,
帮我控油
I'd rather not, if you don't mind, That's not--
要是你不介意的话我想拒绝 那不是…
I'm not one of the oil rubbers, I'm just a guard,
我不是负责氛油的 我只是警卫
Rub me with oil or die,
帮我控油 不然就死
-Is that enough? -Much more, Baste me like a chicken,
-够了吗? -再多点 像涂鸡一样
Oh, yes, Pour it all over me, you little bronze bitchlet,
好 倒满我全身 你这小铜又货
Yeah, okay, You got the whole thing on you now,
好了 全部倒完了
Marvelous, I love it,
太棒了 我喜欢
All right, well, have a good evening, I'm glad I could help you out,
好 晚安 很高兴为您服务
With my hand?
用我的手?
No, With your nutsack, Of course, with your hand,
不 用你的阴宫 当然是用你的手
Oh, yes,
好
Oh, yes, the oily oiliness,
好 油腻腻的油
The musky, precious, smoky, oily oiliness,
珍责的订香 滑汐油腻的油
Yes, that's right, Oh, God, paint a picture on my body,
对 没错 老天 在我身上画图
-Tell a story on my nipples, -Yeah,
-用我的乳头说故事 -好
That's right, take me down the smoky Euphrates,
没错 带我到烟雾弥漫的 幼发拉底河
Do something you'll be ashamed of later...
做些你以后会觉得丢脸的事
..you naughty little goat, All right, charm the snake,
你这淘气的小羊 好 迷壹这条蛇
-Eema, Hey..., -Oh, just like that, Now slap me,
-伊玛 -就像这样 打我
This isn't what it looks like, -My tummy, Go ahead, slap me,
-事实不是这桩的 -我的肚子 快 打我
-Slap me, Slap the tummy, -No, it's fine, ! mean, I understand,
-打我 打我肚子 -不 没关系 我懂
Go on, I love it, I love it, Oh, you're very gifted,
快点 我喜欢 你真有天赋
No, no, no, I'm just rubbing oil on this man's chest, Eema,
不 我只是在这位先生胸口氛油 伊玛
Agift, I don't know, you've got some sort of gift,
天分 我不知道 你真的插有天分的
-Good luck, -Look, Maya, Maya,
-祝你好运 -听着 玛雅 玛雅
Come to me,
过来我身边
Beautiful, isn't it?
很美 对吗?
You can see Gomorrah just over the hill,
可以看到山下上的蛾摩拉
Yep, Twin cities,
对 双子城
People think that the gods are gonna wipe them out...
有人认为上帝将铲平这两个地方
-.. because they're so evil, -And what do you think? Am I evil?
-因为它们太那恶了 -你认为呢? 我那恶吗?
Well, I don't really know you, but you don't look evil,
我还不了解你 但你看起来不邪恶
Do you find me attractive?
你觉得我有讼力吗?
Yeah,
是的
Let me ask you one thing,
我问你一件事
What would a girl like you want with a guy like me?
你这种女生为什么 会找上我这种男生?
I don't know, I just find you interesting,
我不知道 我觉得你很有趣
They say it's the will of the gods...
他们说这是众神的旨意
..that some men should suffer while others rule,
一群人统治时 必有另一群人受苦
That we're all just victims of our own fate,
我们只是自己命运的受害者
I believed that until this morning...
我到今天早上才相信
.. when I saw you standing up alone in the square and I said to myself:
当我看到你站在队伍里 我就告诉自己
A man with the courage to question the order of things,
他有勇气质疑事物的秩序
A man chosen by the gods to do something great,"
神所选的人 他将做出伟大之事
That's exactly what I've been thinking,
我也正是这么想
You would not believe the stuff happening to me,
你一定不相信发生在我身上的事
-I just didn't know why, -l know why,
-我只是不知道原因 -我知道原因
To bring you here, To this place, To me,
为了带你来这里 到这个地方 到我身边
I could not agree more,
我非常同意
I'm trying to agree more, but I can't, because that's how much I agree,
我想更同意一点 但我办不到 因为这是我最同意的程度了
Come,
来
This must be difficult for you to understand...
你一定很难了解…
..but my life is devoted to the service of the gods...
但我的人生都奉献于服务神只
..and the good of the people, I keep nothing for myself,
也奉献给人民 我无视自己的需要
-That's very unselfish of you, -It is unselfish of me, isn't it?
-你真是非常无私 -我无私 是吗?
You're so perceptive for one so young,
你这么年轻 就这么敏锐
-Yeah, What are those doors there? -Behind these doors...
-对 那些门通往哪里? -在这些门后…
..is the Holy of Holies, earthly domain of the gods,
是至圣所 神只在尘世的处所
A place so ineffably sacred, so powerful...
超凡的神圣之地 力量强大…
..that to enter is instant death,
只要一进去就会立即死亡
-Who cleans it? -Needs no cleaning,
-谁负责打要? -不需要打扫
Kind of makes you think about the people that built it,
总会让人想到打造它的人
Like, did they die instantly...
他们是不是立即死亡…
..or were they given a courtesy second...
或许众神还仁感地…
..to get out of there by the gods?
留一秒让他们离开?
They were allowed to finish, given four and a half seconds...
他们受允完成 得到四秒半
..then the gods descended,
然后神只才降临
-What if a bug goes in there? -Instant death for the bug,
-要是虫飞进去呢? -也会马上死亡
Are there dead bugs all over? Because nobody cleans it,
所以里面都是死虫子? 因为没人打扫
They're vaporized immediately...
他们马上就燕发了
..by a holy beam of vapory fire vapor,
因为有神圣的蒸气火束
To enter is instant death, you gorgeous little dunce,
进去就会立即死亡 你这迷人的小傻瓜
Can't even poke our heads in?
连探个头也不行?
You're so young and curious, aren't you?
你真是年轻又好奇 是不是?
..dance with it all, suck it all, don't you?
想跳舞、想吸哆 是不是?
What has two thumbs...
两只拇指…
..and is desperate for another hot-oil rub?
又渴望在哪里抹油?
-What? -This person,
一哪里? -这个人
Come on, Let's go,
快点 我们走
-Come, Come quick, -That will not be a problem,
-过来 快过来 -没有问题
What are we doing here?
我们来这里做什么?
I want you to enter the Holy of Holies,
我要你进入至圣所
Oh, that is quite a coincidence...
还真是巧
... because I want you to sit on the Poley of Poleys,
因为我希望你坐在至阳所上
-Oh, no, That's the Holy of Holies, -[ thought you were talking about--
-不 至圣所在那里 -我以为你是说…
You have to go in there and speak to the gods,
你得进到里面和众神对话
-The gods are in there? -So they say,
-神在里面? -他们是这么说的
The only one who goes in there is the high priest,
只有最高祭司进去过
They say it's instant death for anyone else to enter,
他们说其他人进去就会立即死亡
-Then why am I going in? -Because you've been chosen,
-那我为什么要进去? -因为你是上帝所选之人
If the gods wanted you dead, they would've killed you already,
如果上帝要你死 他们时就杀死你了
-Right, -This is what you've been chosen for,
-没错 -这就是你被选上的理由
To speak to the gods, divine their purpose...
去和众神对话 了解他们的目的
Then come back out and tell me what it's like inside,
然后再回来告诉我 里面是怎么样的
-Okay,
-好
Right,
没错
I'm pretty sure I'm chosen, but I'm not "sure" sure,
我很确定我被选上了 但我不是确定的确定
You're chosen,
你是被选择之人
Okay, I'm gonna go in, but you gotta do something for me,
好 我要进去了 但你要帮我做件事
-You gotta let my friends go, -Anything,
-你要放了我的朋友 -没问题
Don't kill me, don't kill me, don't kill me--
别杀我 别杀我 别杀我
Get up, You look ridiculous,
起来 你看起来很好笑
-Oh? What are you doing here? -I'm hiding from the high priest,
-欧仔? 你在这里做什么? -我在禾最高祭司
I spent the last two hours rubbing oil on him,
过去两个小时 我一直在帮他控油
Is that chest hair?
那是胸毛吗?
Not all of it, Just don't ask, okay?
不全是 但别问了 好吗?
I've lost my sense of right and wrong,
我分不清对错了
How did you get in here without getting fried?
你进来怎么没被烽焦?
-I don't know, How did you? -Because I'm a chosen,
-我不知道 你呢? -因为我是上帝所选之人
Probably why God didn't kill you: He knew you were my follower,
或许上帝不杀你的原因是 他知道你是我的随从
-I'm not your follower, -Why are you always following me?
-我不是你的随从 -那你为什么一直跟着我?
I'm not following you, I walk behind you at the same pace as you,
我不是跟着你 我只是步伐一样 走在你后面而己
Not following, I could be leading from the rear,
不是跟着你 我可以从后面带路
Come on, I'm the leader, l always have been,
拜托 是我带路 一直都是这样
Some leader, Told us you were gonna get us out,
你还真是会带路 你说会带我们离开这里
-Just been messing around at orgies, -Messing around at orgies?
-但你却只顾着纵欲 -只顾着纵欲?
No, no, I'm not like you,
不 我跟你不同
I don't get to prance around in gold paint and have fun,
我没神奇地涂着金漆还很开心
-l have no downtime, -Please, Your whole life is downtime,
-我一刻不得闲 -拜托 你一直都很闲
That's what you think? That's what everybody thinks,
你是这么想的吗? 大家都是这么想的
I'm about to show you something, Observe,
我给你看个东西 看着
Almighty God, or gods, whatever the case may be...
全能的上帝 或是众神 不管是哪一种
..[ need to ask a favor of you,
我要请你帮个忙
I know I've really messed things up...
我知道我搞砸了许多事
..but I really need to come through on this one...
但我真的需要好好处理这件事
..and I wanna ask you to please give me the strength to free my friends,
我想请你赐给我力量解救我的朋友
-And that's it, that's the favor, -Oh, shit,
-就这样 就这个忙 -该死
Hello?
有人吗?
Hasn't it occurred to you that it might be silent...
你有没有想过这么安静…
.. because God is not in here? Look around, There's nothing in here,
是因为上帝不在这里? 看看周围 这里什么也没有
That doesn't prove anything, Maybe he stepped away,
那又不能证明什么 或许他刚好离开了
-For what? -God stuff,
-为什么? -去拿上帝的东西
If he needs something, he can create it from nothing,
要是他需要什么 他可以凭空创造
What's the point of being God if you keep running for things?
要是得一直找东西 那当上帝还有什么意思?
Let me just put something out there, Maybe God doesn't exist,
我把话说清楚 或许上帝不存在
What? So everything is just random?
什么? 那一切都是随机发生的?
Then nothing would mean anything,
那一切就没有意义了
-What would be the point? -That is the point,
-重点是什么? -那就是重点
That there's no point? That's stupid,
根本没意义 真是太昌春了
-You're stupid, -No,
-你才思春 -不
-There's something bigger than me, -There's nothing bigger than you,
-一定有什么比我更了不起的东西 -没什么比你更了不起
-Don't touch my belly to make a point, -Fine,
-别碰我的肚子来证明 -好
-Okay, I'm sorry, l have a man's body, -I'm maturing at my own pace,
-好 对不起 我有男人的身材 -我只是照自己的步调转大人
-You are so jealous of me, -Jealous? That you're a bullshit artist?
-你只是嫉妒我 -嫉妒? 你是个狗屎艺本家?
That every time you speak, it's bullshit coming out of your mouth?
你说话的时候就会吐出狗展来?
You would believe in God if you've ever been with a woman,
如果你和女人上过床 你就会相信上帝了
-I'm a virgin by choice, -Not your choice,
-我是自愿保持处子身 -不是你自愿的
-Take that back, -l won't,
-收回那名话 -我不要
-Take back what you said,
-收回你的话
Everything you've ever said,
你说的每多话
Don't stand close, Get your belly off of my belly,
别站这人么近 你的肚子不要碰我的肚子
Don't touch my belly,
别碰我的肚子
Take everything you've ever said back,
收回你说的每一句话
-You're out of control, -You're a freak,
-你失控了 -你这怪物
-Stop screaming, stop screaming, -You're a freak! Get off me,
-别尖巴了 -你这怪物 放开我
I can pull this thing together, The princess is right out there,
我能解决这件事 公主就在外面
And if I play this right...
如果我演得好
..['m gonna get us all out of here, Maya and Eema too,
我们就能全部离开这里 玛雅和伊玛也可以
Just trust in me, Have a little faith,
相信我 有点信心
Fine, but not for you, For Eema, And I'm too tired to argue right now,
好 但不是为了你 是为了伊玛 而且我累得不想吵了
[had a long hot bath with the high priest, and I'm lightheaded,
我和最高祭司洗了很久的热水澡 我有点尝尝的
I'm sorry for squeezing you so hard,
对不起我的你这么大力
Let's go, Freak,
走吧 怪脸
God, if you do exist, if you make Eema love me...
上帝 如果你真的存在 请让伊玛爱上我
.. would be very grateful, Okay?
我会非常感激的 好吗?
If you do exist,
如果你真的存在
You guys waiting to go in there?
你们等着要进去吗?
Because I gotta say: Not that big a deal,
因为我得说 根本没什么
Seize him,
抓住他
I'm seized,
我被抓了
I wish I was upside down,
但愿是我被倒吊
Looks kind of fun,
看起来很好玩
Is it fun?
好玩吗?
So you're not talking to me?
你不下我说话了?
We're not friends anymore, after all I've done for you?
我们不是朋友了 在我为你做这么多之后?
-What have you done for me? -I brought you out of your shell,
-你为我做了什么? -我带你出来见世面耶
Yeah? I liked my shell, liked the village,
是吗? 我喜欢窝在家里 我喜欢我的村庄
Because of you, I'm in this horrible place where brothers kill brothers...
都是你 我才会来这种 兄弟相残的鬼地方
..and they burn women and they make people slaves,
还会烧女人 还叫人当奴隶
People cut off the ends of their penises...
还有人切下阴茎顶端
..and their testicles and I'm never gonna see Eema again...
还有四万 而且我再也看不到伊玛了
..and it's because of you,
都是因为你
Please forgive me, I mean, you are my best friend,
请原谅我 你是我最好的朋友
I hate the world! I hate you!
我讨厌这个世界 我讨厌你
And now I'm hanging upside down and I really have to pee,
现在我被倒吊着 但我好想原原
I know I'm not perfect,
我知道我不完美
And maybe I made a few wrong turns, but you gotta understand I'm chosen,
或许我犯了一些错 但你要知道我是上天所选
That's a lot of responsibility, You can't even imagine,
我有很多责任 你根本无法想象
The only one that thinks that you're chosen is you, So shut up already!
只有你认为自己被上天所选 所以快点财嘴
I'm gonna get us out of this thing if it's the last thing I do,
我会带我们离开这里的 如果这是我能做的最后一件事
That was just my first idea,
这只是我第一个主意
I'm also accepting ideas,
我也接受大家的建议
Guard! The upside down prisoner has to pee!
警卫 倒吊的犯人要尿原
Oh, I'm peeing,
我尿了
Oh, no,
吗 不
Try to keep your mouth closed,
嘴马财紧一点
Oh, no, In the nose,
喔 糟故 进鼻子了
Hey, I'm peeing on my face too, on the inside,
我也原在我脸上过 在妈妈肚子里
I hate you,
我恨你
.Since it was you who lured him to his death,
因为是你害死他的
"For the crimes of blasphemy...
“因为讼潜上帝的罪
..conspiracy...,"
阴谋
-What you thinking about? -"Treachery...
-你在想什么? 加 背叛
. leprosy..."
*狂注“
Trying to make conversation,
我只是想聊一聊
“Puppetry...
"使偶?
-.. hyperbole..." -Your hair looks really good today,
一"等饰“ -今天你的头发真的很漂亮
-I peed all over it, -Then that's the secret, I guess,
-上面都是尿 -我想那是秘诀
"Sodomy...,"
A 鸡奸
-Oh, it's "refusal of sodomy," -Yeah!
-唾 是“拒绝鸡奸 -好
Can you just forgive me?
你能原谅我吗?
I think I hate you too much,
我想我太恨你了
"Lechery and the murder of my brother, Abel,"
"淫荡 还有杀了我哥埃布尔*
-Oh, come on! -Shut it!
-吗 拜托 -闭嘴
..the prisoners shall be stoned...
犯人应被石击…
..to death!
至死
-Wait! Can I make a suggestion? -What?
-等等 我能提个建议吗? -什么?
Just have one person throw stones at us,
只叫一个人对我们丢石头
In fact, I think it would be fair if you let us choose who gets to stone us,
事实上 你应该让我们选 谁对我们委石头才公平
No, That doesn't make any--
不 这样说不.…
-We want that guy, -That guy,
-我们要那个人 -那个人
-Me? -That's our stoner,
一我? -就是他
What, just because I'm a eunuch you don't think I can throw?
就因为我是太监 你们就以为我不会条了吗?
I'll show you throwing,
我让你看看什么叫丢石头
No, no, No, no, no! Gross,
不…好恶心
Did he just hurl his own ball at him? How spectacular,
他刚把自己的蛋蛋丢到他身上? 真是特别
No! That doesn't count, That was a testicle,
不 那不算 那是轩九
I think it counts,
我觉得算
-Pick somebody else, -What is that idiot doing?
-再选别人 -那白病在做什么?
-I pick that guy! -Nice,
-我选那个人 -很好
-This guy? -No, no, the shorter man,
-这个人 -不 矮的那个
Right in front of him,
就在他前面
It's a kid, This is a kid,
这是小孩 这只是小孩
So? You got something against kids? This guy hates kids,
又怎样? 你对小孩有意见吗? 这家伙讨厌小孩
-Let me smite him! -Kid hater!
-我来打他 -他讨厌小孩
-One shot! -No, they're our future!
-投一次 -不 他们是我们的未来
All right, Hey, go ahead and--
好 来…
Okay, I'm hit,
好 我被打中了
Holy shit, that kid's got an arm,
该死 那孩子辟力真强
God, There's two of us,
老天 不能只打我一个啊
Are you guys happy now?
你们开心了?
Okay! Everybody on this side, on the count of three! One, two--
好了 这边的所有人 我数到三 一
Wait! I have a question for the king,
等等 我要问国王一个问题
Why didn't I die in the Holy of Holies?
我为什么没死在至圣所里?
Yes! I entered the Holy of Holies and, lo, I did not die,
对 我进过至圣所 而且你们看 我没死
Why? Because I was chosen by the gods!
为什么? 因为我是众神所选之人
Spare the chosen one!
饶了所选之人 馈了所选之人
-Spare the chosen one! -And his friend!
-饶了所选之人 -还有他的朋友
-And his young friend, -Don't kill either of them,
-还有他年轻的朋友 -一个也不能杀
Everyone knows the chosen gets a plus one,
大家都知道所选之人 还带了一个人
Is it possible? Is he truly chosen?
有可能吗? 他真的是所选之人
Well, of course it's possible, Highly doubtful,
当然有可能 只是我部度怀疑
Majesty, with respect...
陛下 容我秉述
.. Whether he is chosen or not is no longer the issue,
他是否为所选之人已不重要
If you were to kill him now, given the public mood...
如果你现在要杀他 依现在大众的情绪…
..it could inflame the situation $0 as...
可能会点燃情势 因而…
..to cause a radical regime change,
引发激烈的政变
If you take my meaning,
如果你明白我的意思
Yes, that will do,
是的 够了
It is the judgment of our merciful king that the prisoners be enslaved...
我们仁巧的国王作了裁决 犯人将被奴役…
Yes!
好
And how is that better?
这有比较好吗?
You seem to enjoy your work, How long have you been a slave?
你似乎做得很开心 你当奴录多久了?
Oh, I'm not a slave, I'm a volunteer,
我不是奴隶 我是义工
Marlak, Enmebaragesi, Long time no see,
马拉、安柏盖斯 好扩不见
Take these bricks up top, The masons are waiting,
搬砖块上去 石匠在等砖块
I would but I did something to my neck, I think I slept on it funny,
我很想 但我脖子怪怪的 我可能落枕了
I should probably take it easy, or I'll be no good for work tomorrow,
我或许该休息一下 不然明天就不能工作了
Move!
快去
You know, the mud's really good for your skin,
你知道 这些泥妆对皮肤很好
-Yeah, -Ask me why my skin's so good,
-对 -问我为什么我皮肤这么好
-Why's your skin--? -The mud,
-为什么你的皮肤… -因为泥染
I knew you were gonna say that,
我早知道你会这么说
You gotta love being outside,
你会喜欢待在外面
Move it!
快点
Faster!
再快一点
-Want some water? -You're from the village, aren't you?
-要水吗? -你是村庄来的 对吧?
I'll bet you wish you were back there right now,
我打赌你希望现在能回到那里
-Yeah, -Don't give up,
-对 -别放弃
You'll get home someday,
有一天你会回家的
Who's gonna take him there? The chosen one?
谁带他回去? 上帝所人选之人?
You two, up! Get on line, Now,
你们俩 起来 排队 快
-Where are we going? -To watch the sacrifice,
-要去哪里? -去看献祭
-The king demands it, -ls it compulsory?
-国王要求的 -是强制性的吗?
There was some work that I wanted to finish doing, get a jump on tomorrow,
我想先做完这些工作 好赶上明天的工作
I'd like to see how big you are without that whip,
要是没鞠子 你还有多了不起
Same basic size,
还是很了不起
Allis in readiness, Your Majesty,
陛下 一切都准备就绪
What now? More virgins to sacrifice?
现在呢? 带处女去献祭?
Followers of the chosen one, Discovered by this loyal soldier,
所选之人的随从 患心的士兵发现的
Oh, I was just doing my job, It's what I do,
我只是做好份内之事 我该做的
And one more to demonstrate our own faith and charity,
再一次 展现我们的信仰与仁慧
For the love of the people, and the heavenly gift of rain...
为了爱护人民 还有雨水的神圣大和礼
..We offer a humble sacrifice:
我们谦卑地奉上妹品
our own stepdaughter...
我自己的继女
..the Princess Inanna,
伊南娜公主
-You're insane, -For the good of the people, darling,
-你疯了 -这是为了人民好 亲爱的
-You wouldn't dare, -Wouldn't I?
-你不到 -我不敢吗?
If you like, I can arrange for you to join her,
要是你喜欢 我可以安排你和她一起
Mother,
母亲
How long did you think I would tolerate your insolence?
你以为我能容忍你的无礼多久?
Burn her,
烧死她
Drink it, You won't feel a thing,
喝下去 就不会有感觉了
Are they booing me? How dare they,
他们在向我喝倒采吗? 他们真大胆
They love you, They're wooing you,
他们爱你 他们在向你喝采
That's fine, You know?
可以了
It's Maya! And Eema! Wait, Maya's a virgin?
等等 玛雅是处女吗?
No, don't kill them!
不 别杀她们
-Far enough, slave, -No, kill me! I'm a male virgin,
-站远点 奴录 -不 杀我 我是处男
Marlak, we can't let them do this! Eema!
马拉 我们不能让他们这么做 伊玛
Eema, Eema!
伊玛 伊玛
-I gotta get down there, -Over my dead body,
-我得下去 -除非我死
-No problem, -No, Hey! Hey! Hey!
-没问题 -不
-Thanks, Marlak, -Now what?
-马拉 谢谢 -现在呢?
We implore the great gods to show us a sign...
我们乞求伟大的神只 向我们显现神迹
..0 that we may honor your divine will,
好让我们荣耀您神圣的旨意
Take this end, Lower me down,
抓着这个 把我放下去
Oh, dear,
老天和区
Oh, no,
不
-What is it? -It's a sign,
-怎么回事? -神迹
The chosen one comes! It's a sign! He's going to end our suffering!
所选之人来了 是神迹 他来结束我们的苦难了
Fight the power! Yes, we can!
对抗权力 我们可以的
All together!
集合
Let's cut some foreskins!
伸掉他们的包皮
I knew I could depend upon your loyalty,
我早知道我能仰赖你们的患诚
Assholes,
混蛋
Burn them, Burn them now, Burn them all!
烧了他们 快烧了他们 把他们全烧了
Don't struggle, it's the will of the gods,
别稳扎 这是神的旨意
I don't think so,
我不这么认为
Guards!
警卫
-Sorry! -Stupid,
-抱娄 -策蛋
Ma'am? Okay? All right? Get the message?
小姐? 好了吗? 懂了吗?
Okay, we should be safe in here,
好 我们应该安全了
Thank you,
谢谢你
So, Eema, this might be a bad time to say this...
伊玛 现在说这句话或许时机不对
..With the high priest, that--
和最高祭司的事…
He's a friend, That was totally not a gay thing,
他只是朋友 完全和同性恋无关
l always thought that you and I had a connection,
我一直以为我们之间有种连结
So I just wanted to mention it now,
所以我现在想说
l always thought that we had one and maybe...
我一直认为我们有种 或许…
.. thought you might've felt the same,
我想你或许也有一样的感觉
I just wanted to maybe bring it up and see what you would say,
我只是想说… 看看你会不会说…
But I always thought-- I always have felt a certain way about you,
但我一直认为 我一直对你有特殊的感觉
I don't know if you know or not but you--
我不知道你知不知道 可是你…
All those dead birds that were always outside of your hut...
你屋外总是有死掉的小岛…
-Just kiss me, -From me like a gift for you,
-亲我就好 -我想送你礼物
I don't know, I thought you'd like those,
我不知道 我起你会喜欢
l always thought that you could maybe use the dead birds...
我一直在想你能用那些死小乌…
..in a soup or something,
做汤或什么的
Or, I don't know, I thought they were practical,
或是…我不知道 我觉得这些礼物很实用
Should I take off my undercloth?
我要把我内衣脱掉吗?
Oh, tough guy, huh? You want a piece of me?
硬汉 是吗? 你想杀了我?
I'm gonna bash your head in,
我要打爆你的头
That was a nice shot,
那招真厉害
Hey,
哩 ov
Get up and die like a man,
起来 像个男人一样赴死
Nobody harm this woman, She's not a virgin anymore,
没人能伤害这个女人 她不再是处女了
-He's not either, -I saved her life with my lovemaking,
-他也不是了 -我和她做爱 救了她的命
Sit tight, Mama, Daddy's gotta fight,
坐稳 妈妈 葡爸要开打了
Okay, No, wait, wait, wait! Wait, don't kill him!
好 不 等等 别杀他
What?
什么?
I just had sex with my new girlfriend,
我刚和我新女朋友做爱了
-So? -I had to tell somebody, It was great,
-所以呢? -我得跟别人说感觉很棒
I loved it, I'm hoping I'm gonna get another opportunity,
我很喜欢 希望我还能有再一次的机会
-What's going on behind you? -I'm not falling for that,
-你后面怎么了? -我不会上当的
-Stop! No! -Get back!
-住手 不要 -退后
-Let her go! -No!
-放开她 -不
The gods demand a sacrifice, You're ruining it!
神需要妹品 却被你毁了
-How about a little more oil? -Yes, darling?
-那再加点油 如何? -好 亲爱的
l always knew you'd break my heart,
我时知道你会让我心碎
A little hot!
有点演
That was ironic,
真是讽刺
So...
那么.…
..on behalf of the whole city...
我代表整个城市
.al'd like to thank the high priest for his sacrifice,
感谢最高祭司的牺牲
That was really something, wasn't it?
真的很了不起 对不对?
Come on, Put your hands together, it makes a sound,
快点 把手放在一起 拍出声音来
The chosen one! The chosen one!
所选之人.…
Okay, that was a little confusing, wasn't it?
好 有点困囊 对不对?
Was that a sign from the gods?
那是神迹吗?
Everybody wants to know,
大家都想知道
Well, l should know, because I'm the chosen one, right?
我应该知道的 因为我是所选之人 对吗?
Yeah!
对
You respect me,
你们尊丽我
You love me,
你们爱我
Yeah!
对
You fear me,
你们恶惧我
You would worship me,
你们尝才我
Yeah!
对
Well, don't,
不要
-Yeah! -No,
-好 -不要
And I'm not saying, "Don't" like, "I'm the chosen one, so don't,"
我说不要 不是指 我是所选之人 所以不要
I'm saying, "Don't" because I'm not the chosen one,
我说“不要”是指我不是所选之人
I thought I was, but I'm not, sorry,
我以为我是 但我不是 抱攻
Turns out I'm just a guy from the woods...
其实我只是个丛林里的野人
.. who was lucky enough to have these great friends to watch my back,
走运有这群好朋友罩着我
I'm telling you, you don't need me,
我告诉大家 你们不需要我
You know what? Maybe we can all make our own destiny,
你们知道吗? 或许我们能决定自己的命运
Yeah, Maybe we could all be chosen,
对 或许我们都是所选之人
Yeah,
对
-You! You could be chosen! -Yeah!
-你 你也是所选之人 -对
-And you! And you!
-还有你 你
Way over in the back! You, little guy!
最后面那个 小家伙
Yeah!
好耶
-So you're queen, -Couldn't have done it without you,
-你是皇后了 -没有你我做不到
Yeah, you could've,
你可以的
No, really, I tried for years and...,
不 真的 我努力了好几年
All right, maybe you couldn't have, I was pretty amazing with the old--
好 或许你不能 我是很厉害
Sorry about almost luring you to your death,
抱鞭我差点害死你
Oh, please,
拜托
All right,
好了
Okay,
好
See you later,
待会儿见
Come on, people,
走吧 各位
-Pick up that bag of camel dung, -Yes, sir,
-把那袋骆驼凌捡起来 -是 长官
Hang on to it all day,
整天都要提着它
Hustle up, These donkeys don't pack themselves,
快点 这些驴子不会自己打包
-[ will kill you where you stand, -Relax,
-我要就地杀了你 -放轻松
They cut a little off the end but there's plenty more where that came from,
他们切了一点龟头 不过还剩很多
This is my woman, Stay away from her, or I'll kill you,
这是我的女人 离她远一点 不然我就地杀了你
-Okay, okay, I'm sorry, -Just go,
-好 对不起 -离开
Get out of here or I'll kill you,
走开 不然我就杀了你
Cranky today,
今天脾气真坏
So are you still thinking about going to Egypt?
你还在想去埃及的事?
Supposed to be a real happening place, You coming with or not?
我想真的会成行 你要不要去?
Well, l mean, I was kind of planning on going anyway, so...,
反正我本来也打算去 所以…
Let me show you this new style, Everyone's doing it,
给你看看新的方式 大家都这么做
You open your mouth really wide, It makes it way sexier,
把嘴已张得开开的 会更性感
I'm thinking about introducing the tongue, but I haven't perfected it yet,
我想把舌头伸进去 但我技术还未纯熟
-You know, we'll work on that, -All right,
-我们可以研究研究 -好
Look at us, Two men,
看看我们 两个男人
One going to lead a village and the other going to explore the world,
一人要去带领村庄 另一人要去探索世界
You sure you don't wanna come back, help me?
你确定你不想回去帮有我?
You don't need me, Everybody knows you're the smartest guy in the village,
你不需要我 大家都知道 你是村庄里最聪明的人
Gonna know you're the most incredible warrior anyone's ever seen,
他们还会知道 你是前所未见最厉害的战士
She left me no choice, so I had to, you know, punch her in the face,
她让我别无选择 我不得不打她的脸
Well, we'll tell stories about you around the fire,
我们会围着营火说你的故事
Strangers shake hands, Get that thing out of here,
耳生人才握手 你少来了
-I'm gonna miss you, little guy, -I'm gonna miss you more,
-我会想你的 小家伙 -我会更想你
Just trying to sniff you, l wanna remember your scent,
我要闻闻你 我要记得你的味道
That's probably the urine in my hair,
那可能是我头发上的尿
I can't let them see me cry, They respect me too much,
我不能让他们看到我史 他们太尊丽我了
Me too, On three, One, two, three, break,
我也是 数到三 一二三分开
Well, may the gods smile on you, See you around,
愿上帝祝福你 再见了
Whatever, Later,
随便晓 待会儿见
-Oh? -What?
-欧仔? -什么?
I want you to have babies with my sister,
我要你和我妹生个孩子
-Try and stop me, -All right, man,
-这还用你说 -好 兄弟
-Zed, may the gods smile on you, -You said that,
-柴德 愿上帝祝福你 -你说过了
-May they, Yeah, -Thank you, though,
-但愿如此 -还是谢谢你
All right come on, folks, We're heading out now because I say so, all right?
好了 大家快点 我们要出发了 我说了算 好吗?
What's the deal? Come on, Lindsey, Come on, everyone's looking,
怎么了? 快点 琳西 快点 大家都在看
Please, Go, Good,
拜托 走 很好
To the north!
往北方前进
You know that that's west,
你知道那里是西方
I was just checking to see if you knew,
我只是试试你知不知道
To the west!
往西方前进
I'm already glad you're here,
我真高兴你跟着来
One, two, three, foreskin!
一二三包皮
Invoke your blessing and do your will,
新求您赐福 依您的旨意
What's the fucking line? What is it?
台词到底是什么? 是什么?
It was a game, It was a game of chance...
只是游戏 机率游戏
..and he hit his head and he killed himself,
他打到头 杀了自己
If anything, it was a suicide, Okay,
这只算自杀 好
I let one go,
我漏了一包
In honor of the chosen one, as my first official act as your queen...
为了向所选之人致意 我身为皇后的第一项决策
..l'm going to go back and say the line again,
我要回头再说一次台词
-Let's go back, Do you wanna try it? -Yeah,
-回去 你想试试吗? -好
And suck it all in and blow it all out your backside, don't you?
想级哆、想从后面吹 对不对?
Sorry,
抱攻
It's like the Great Turtle coming out of the sea, you know?
就像大乌龟朴出海面 你知道吗?
It's like with the earth on its back, you understand?
好像背后还背着地球 你懂吗?
I'm an oilman,
我是石油工
You're cursed, Zed, and if you don't leave here we're all gonna be cursed,
柴德 你被诅咒了 要是你不离开 我们都会被谊唤
And it drank up the ocean, then pooped out the mountains...
它喝干了海洋 然后在山上大便
..and the first man fell from the stars,
而第一个男人就从星辰中坠落
This is-- l don't-- This doesn't make a lot of sense, guys,
这是 我不… 这一点都不合理
Can I talk to Harold? Is that--?
我能和哈洛谈谈吗? 这是…
What's that?
那是什么?
A strange Gorgon from another time!
那是什么? 那是其他时空来的 长耳芒怪
I weep for the suffering of my people,
我为了人民的苦难枢注
We're getting boned...
又被破坏
.. by the planes, the trains, and the what, huh?
有飞机、火车 还有什么?
Zed?
柴德?
-Oh, that's great, -Zed? It's constricting me,
-太棒了 -柴德 它在勒我
Can I show you this new kiss I been thinking about?
我能让你看看 我想了很久的新亲法吗?
-Yeah, -It's called a tongue kiss,
-好 -这叫苦吻
-It's strange, Yeah, Okay, -Still perfecting it, yeah,
-真奇怪 对 好 -还要再练习
-It's fine, -All right,
-没关系 -好
What?
什么?